module.exports = {
  data: [
    {
      "question": "Who won the IPL 2024 title?",
      "option1": "Sunrisers Hyderabad",
      "option2": "Royal Challengers Bangalore",
      "option3": "Kolkata Knight Riders",
      "option4": "Punjab Kings",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was named the Most Valuable Player (MVP) of IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Virat Kohli",
      "option2": "Sunil Narine",
      "option3": "Harshal Patel",
      "option4": "Nitish Kumar Reddy",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player won the Orange Cap in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Abhishek Sharma",
      "option2": "Travis Head",
      "option3": "Virat Kohli",
      "option4": "Jake Fraser-McGurk",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team was the runner-up in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Delhi Capitals",
      "option2": "Royal Challengers Bangalore",
      "option3": "Sunrisers Hyderabad",
      "option4": "Punjab Kings",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the prize amount for the winner of IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Rs. 15 crore",
      "option2": "Rs. 20 crore",
      "option3": "Rs. 25 crore",
      "option4": "Rs. 12.5 crore",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which stadium won the Pitch and Ground Award in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Wankhede Stadium",
      "option2": "Eden Gardens",
      "option3": "Rajiv Gandhi International Stadium",
      "option4": "M. Chinnaswamy Stadium",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the Purple Cap in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Harshal Patel",
      "option2": "Jasprit Bumrah",
      "option3": "Mohammed Shami",
      "option4": "Rashid Khan",
      "ans": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team received the Fair Play Award in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Chennai Super Kings",
      "option2": "Delhi Capitals",
      "option3": "Mumbai Indians",
      "option4": "Sunrisers Hyderabad",
      "ans": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Who announced his retirement after IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "MS Dhoni",
      "option2": "Dinesh Karthik",
      "option3": "Ajinkya Rahane",
      "option4": "Mohammed Shami",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was the final match of IPL 2024 played?",
      "option1": "Eden Gardens",
      "option2": "M.A. Chidambaram Stadium",
      "option3": "Narendra Modi Stadium",
      "option4": "Arun Jaitley Stadium",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player hit the most sixes in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Heinrich Klaasen",
      "option2": "Abhishek Sharma",
      "option3": "Jake Fraser-McGurk",
      "option4": "Shivam Dube",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the captain of Kolkata Knight Riders in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Andre Russell",
      "option2": "Shreyas Iyer",
      "option3": "Nitish Rana",
      "option4": "Rinku Singh",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the Emerging Player Award in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Harshit Rana",
      "option2": "Riyan Parag",
      "option3": "Nitish Kumar Reddy",
      "option4": "Yashasvi Jaiswal",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which bowler had the best economy rate in IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Jasprit Bumrah",
      "option2": "Sunil Narine",
      "option3": "Axar Patel",
      "option4": "Mohammed Siraj",
      "ans": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team had the highest net run rate (NRR) in the league stage of IPL 2024?",
      "option1": "Kolkata Knight Riders",
      "option2": "Sunrisers Hyderabad",
      "option3": "Rajasthan Royals",
      "option4": "Lucknow Super Giants",
      "ans": 1
    }
  ]
}
